http://www.daymarcollege.edu/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy | Daymar College
About Us
Locations
About Us Overview »
History
Mission
Accreditation
What is Competency-Based Learning?
Daymar College Blog
Locations Overview »
Admissions
Programs Overview »
Network Support Administration - Engineer
Admissions Overview »
Contact Us
Current Students Overview »
Columbus Business Management
Human Resource ManagementBowling Green Human Resource Management
Criminal JusticeCriminal JusticeBowling Green Criminal Justice
Columbus Criminal Justice
Paralegal Studies
Health CareBilling & Coding SpecialistBowling Green Medical Billing & Coding
Physical Therapist Assistant
Health & WellnessMedical Massage TherapyColumbus Medical Massage Therapy
Technology & DesignNetwork Support AdministrationBowling Green Network Support Administration - CISCO
Privacy Policy
Our Privacy Policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine the highest-quality products and services with the highest level of integrity in dealing with our visitors, members and partners. It is designed not only to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us, but also to help you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services. This Privacy Policy will be continually assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers' needs.
Access to and use of the Daymar College is available only to United States residents who can form legally binding contracts under applicable law. If you do not qualify, you may not use the Web site. If you are a minor, you may use the Daymar College web site only in conjunction with your parent, legal guardian, or other responsible adult. We urge supervising adults to actively oversee minors' online use.
As described below, some of your personally identifiable information will be used by us and shared with third parties. By using the Web site, you expressly consent to our use of your personal information, and also to the disclosure to and use of this information by third parties. You acknowledge that communications to, from and through the Daymar College web site is not confidential. You agree that by submitting communications through the Daymar College web site, no confidential, fiduciary, contractually implied, or other relationship is created between you and Daymar College other than pursuant to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms and conditions of our Terms and Conditions.
A Note About Minors
In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, no one under 13 years of age can use the Web site. If you are a minor between the ages of 13 and 18, you may use the Site only in conjunction with your parent, legal guardian, or other responsible adult.
What Information Do We Collect?
The goal of the Daymar College web site is to be your favorite college search destination on the Internet by providing you with the information, services and product offerings that are most relevant to you. To achieve this goal, we collect two types of information from you when you visit the Site: personally identifiable information you voluntarily choose to disclose, and "aggregate information" about your use of the Site, which is automatically collected when you visit the Web site.
1. Personal Information You Choose to Provide
Personally identifiable information refers to information that tells us specifically who you are. Personal information is collected when you voluntarily choose to request information from a school that is listed on the Site. As a site user, you are asked to provide certain basic information such as your name, current e-mail address and programs of interest. You may also provide additional personal information at your discretion. Further, if you choose to correspond with us through e-mail, we may retain the content of your e-mail messages together with your e-mail address and our responses.
How Do We Use The Personal Information That You Provide To Us?
Broadly speaking, your personal information is used to help match your interests with a program that provides the training you seek. If your search yields no results, we may store your information and send you updates if and when programs you specified do become available.
We also use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer service, and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to the Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable.
2. Aggregate Information
Aggregate information refers to information your computer automatically provides to us and that cannot be tied back to you as a specific individual. Examples include referral data (the web sites you visited just before and just after the Web site) the date and time of your visits, the pages viewed, time spent at the Web site, browser and platform type (e.g., a Netscape browser on a Macintosh platform), and IP (Internet Protocol) addresses. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you surf the Web. When you request a page from one of our Sites, our servers log your IP address to create aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for advertisers and partners, and for purposes of system administration. This allows these parties to advertise more effectively and allows you to receive advertisements that are most relevant to your personal interests.
3. Cookies
The Daymar College web site, along with thousands of other web sites, uses standard technologies, such as cookies and web server logs to enhance your web viewing experience. Cookies and web server logs automatically track certain information about you that is based upon your activity on the Site. A cookie is a small piece of data transferred from a web site to the hard drive of your computer so that the web site may track your activities on the site. Web server logs allow us to count how many people visit the Web site and also to evaluate the Site's visitor capacity.
Each time you access the Site, our server may deliver certain customized information to you based on the data stored in your cookies. Cookies allow us to determine which areas and features of our Site are most popular by measuring user activity. The information in the cookies lets us trace the paths followed by users as they move from one page to another. Cookies let sites and advertisers "remember" users across pages of a site and across multiple visits to a site. This allows e-commerce and Internet advertising to: personalize features such as targeted news stories, provide shopping sessions and quick navigation across multiple zones of e-commerce sites, remember user names and passwords for future visits, control ad frequency or the number of times a user sees a given ad, and deliver advertisements targeted to a user's interests.
Notice Of New Services And Changes
Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to the Web site, new services, and special offers we think you will find valuable.
How Do We Protect Your Information?
We utilize encryption/security software to safeguard the confidentiality of personal information we collect. This software provides a limited degree of protection against unauthorized access or disclosure, as well as accidental loss, alteration or destruction.
Do We Comply With Legally Compelled Disclosure Of Information?
We may release any private information about you that we possess when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, to enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions, Privacy Policy and/or other agreements, or to protect the rights, property or safety of Daymar College., the Site users, or others.
What About Other Web Sites Linked To Or From The Web Site?
The links on the Daymar College site allow you to leave the Site. Please be aware that once you leave the Site and enter another web site, or use certain services provided through the Site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on web sites that have a link to the Web site, or any links contained in a linked site, is subject to that web site's own rules and policies. Daymar College is not responsible for the privacy practices employed by neither these sites, nor the information or content contained therein. We provide these links to you only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Daymar College. Please read over the rules and policies of these sites before proceeding.
Classes Start Soon!
Financial Aid Scholarships
Request Information
Campus
Campus *
- Select -OnlineBowling GreenColumbusClarksvilleMurfreesboroNashville
Programs
Programs Online *
- Select -Not SureAccountingBilling and Coding SpecialistBusiness ManagementCriminal JusticeHuman Resources ManagementMedical Assisting - AdministrativeParalegal StudiesPharmacy TechnologyBusiness ManagementCriminal Justice AdministrationHealth Care AdministrationBilling & Coding SpecialistBusiness ManagementCriminal JusticeHuman Resources ManagementMedical Assisting - AdministrationPharmacy Technology
Programs Bellevue *
- Select -Not SureBusiness AdministrationBilling and Coding SpecialistCriminal JusticeMedical AssistingMedical Massage Therapy
Programs Bowling Green *
- Select -Not SureAccountingBilling and Coding SpecialistCardiographic TechnologyCriminal JusticeMedical Assisting - AdministrativeNetwork Support AdministrationPharmacy TechnologyBusiness ManagementCriminal Justice AdministrationAccountingCardiographic TechnologyCriminal JusticeMedical AssistingPharmacy Technology
Programs Columbus *
- Select -Not SureAccountingBilling and Coding SpecialistCriminal JusticeMedical AssistingBusiness ManagementMedical AssistingMedical Massage Therapy
Programs Clarksville *
- Select -Not SureBilling and Coding SpecialistBusiness ManagementCriminal JusticeDental AssistingHuman Resource ManagementMedical AssistingNetwork Support Administration - CISCO/EngineerParalegal StudiesPharmacy TechnologyPhysical Therapist AssistantBusiness ManagementHealth Care Administration - Billing & Coding/Medical Assisting/Pharmacy TechCriminal Justice AdministrationBilling & Coding SpecialistBusiness ManagementDental AssistingHuman Resources ManagementMedical Assisting
Programs Murfreesboro *
- Select -Not SureAccountingBilling and Coding SpecialistBusiness ManagementCriminal JusticeMedical AssistingPharmacy TechnologyCriminal JusticeMedical AssistingPenn Foster High School Completion Program
Programs Nashville *
- Select -Not SureAccountingBilling and Coding SpecialistBusiness ManagementCriminal JusticeMedical AssistingNetwork Support AdministrationBusiness ManagementHealth Care Administration - Pharmacy TechnologyBilling and Coding SpecialistMedical AssistingPharmacy TechnologyPenn Foster High School Completion Program
First Name
First Name *
Last Name
Last Name *
Phone
Phone *
Zip Code
Zip Code *
Email
Email *
Clicking the “Send Request” button below constitutes your express written consent to be called and/or texted by Daymar at the number(s) provided, including a wireless number if provided, regarding furthering your education. You understand that these calls may be live or generated using an automated technology. Standard message & data rates apply. I may revoke this consent at any time. I understand I am not required to provide consent as a condition of considering purchasing education services from Daymar. As an alternative, I may call Daymar at the number provided.
This location is currently not accepting new applications.
You may be interested in another location near you:
Online Campus
Bowling Green, KY
Clarksville, TN
This location is currently not accepting new applications.
You may be interested in another location near you:
Online Campus
Bowling Green, KY
Clarksville, TN
This location is currently not accepting new applications.
You may be interested in another location near you:
Online Campus
Bowling Green, KY
Clarksville, TN
Join Our Network
Classes Start Soon!
Financial Aid Scholarships
Join Our Network
Request Information
Campus
Campus *
- Select -OnlineBowling GreenColumbusClarksvilleMurfreesboroNashville
Programs
Programs Online *
- Select -Not SureAccountingBilling and Coding SpecialistBusiness ManagementCriminal JusticeHuman Resources ManagementMedical Assisting - AdministrativeParalegal StudiesPharmacy TechnologyBusiness ManagementCriminal Justice AdministrationHealth Care AdministrationBilling & Coding SpecialistBusiness ManagementCriminal JusticeHuman Resources ManagementMedical Assisting - AdministrationPharmacy Technology
Programs Bellevue *
- Select -Not SureBusiness AdministrationBilling and Coding SpecialistCriminal JusticeMedical AssistingMedical Massage Therapy
Programs Bowling Green *
- Select -Not SureAccountingBilling and Coding SpecialistCardiographic TechnologyCriminal JusticeMedical Assisting - AdministrativeNetwork Support AdministrationPharmacy TechnologyBusiness ManagementCriminal Justice AdministrationAccountingCardiographic TechnologyCriminal JusticeMedical AssistingPharmacy Technology
Programs Columbus *
- Select -Not SureAccountingBilling and Coding SpecialistCriminal JusticeMedical AssistingBusiness ManagementMedical AssistingMedical Massage Therapy
Programs Clarksville *
- Select -Not SureBilling and Coding SpecialistBusiness ManagementCriminal JusticeDental AssistingHuman Resource ManagementMedical AssistingNetwork Support Administration - CISCO/EngineerParalegal StudiesPharmacy TechnologyPhysical Therapist AssistantBusiness ManagementHealth Care Administration - Billing & Coding/Medical Assisting/Pharmacy TechCriminal Justice AdministrationBilling & Coding SpecialistBusiness ManagementDental AssistingHuman Resources ManagementMedical Assisting
Programs Murfreesboro *
- Select -Not SureAccountingBilling and Coding SpecialistBusiness ManagementCriminal JusticeMedical AssistingPharmacy TechnologyCriminal JusticeMedical AssistingPenn Foster High School Completion Program
Programs Nashville *
- Select -Not SureAccountingBilling and Coding SpecialistBusiness ManagementCriminal JusticeMedical AssistingNetwork Support AdministrationBusiness ManagementHealth Care Administration - Pharmacy TechnologyBilling and Coding SpecialistMedical AssistingPharmacy TechnologyPenn Foster High School Completion Program
First Name
First Name *
Last Name
Last Name *
Phone
Phone *
Zip Code
Zip Code *
Email
Email *
Clicking the “Send Request” button below constitutes your express written consent to be called and/or texted by Daymar at the number(s) provided, including a wireless number if provided, regarding furthering your education. You understand that these calls may be live or generated using an automated technology. Standard message & data rates apply. I may revoke this consent at any time. I understand I am not required to provide consent as a condition of considering purchasing education services from Daymar. As an alternative, I may call Daymar at the number provided.
This location is currently not accepting new applications.
You may be interested in another location near you:
Online Campus
Bowling Green, KY
Clarksville, TN
This location is currently not accepting new applications.
You may be interested in another location near you:
Online Campus
Bowling Green, KY
Clarksville, TN
This location is currently not accepting new applications.
You may be interested in another location near you:
